<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tembea Kenya</string>

    //day numbers
    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="day_31">Day 31</string>

    //titles
    <string name = "title_1">Nairobi</string>
    <string name = "title_2">Samburu</string>
    <string name = "title_3">Eldoret</string>
    <string name = "title_4">Kakamega</string>
    <string name = "title_5">Nakuru</string>
    <string name = "title_6">Meru</string>
    <string name = "title_7">Narok</string>
    <string name = "title_8">Mombasa</string>
    <string name = "title_9">Kitale</string>
    <string name = "title_10">Thika</string>
    <string name = "title_11">Kisumu</string>
    <string name = "title_12">Giraffe Manor</string>
    <string name = "title_13">Amboseli National Park</string>
    <string name = "title_14">Mt. Kenya</string>
    <string name = "title_15">Lake Victoria</string>
    <string name = "title_16">Lake Naivasha</string>
    <string name = "title_17">Samburu National Reserve</string>
    <string name = "title_18">Diani Beach</string>
    <string name = "title_19">Manda Bay</string>
    <string name = "title_20">The Great Rift Valley</string>
    <string name = "title_21">Uhuru Gardens</string>
    <string name = "title_22">Lamu Island</string>
    <string name = "title_23">Wasini Island</string>
    <string name = "title_24">Mount Longonot</string>
    <string name = "title_25">Hells Gate National Park</string>
    <string name = "title_26">Tsavo National Park</string>
    <string name = "title_27">Lake Nakuru</string>
    <string name = "title_28">Fourteen Falls</string>
    <string name = "title_29">Shaba National Reserve</string>
    <string name = "title_30">Buffalo Springs National Reserve</string>
    <string name = "title_31">Ol Pejeta Conservancy</string>

    //descriptions
    <string name = "nairobi_01">The museum named Karen Blixen Museum is one of the biggest hits – not only the African fans come to praise and appreciate the museum but also people from all over the world visit the museum to view the namesake Danish author who with drudgeries toiled on the coffee farmstead in the midst of the beautiful Ngong Hills. Even in such a scampering city like Nairobi, wildlife is a colossal draw. Being a cosmopolitan capital, Nairobi is the only city in the globe that brags a safari park within its frontiers.</string>
    <string name = "samburu_02">Samburu County is a game reserve situated on the banks of River Ewaso Ng’iro, in the former Rift Valley province, in northern Kenya. It stretches from the south of Lake Turkana to River Ewaso Ng’iro in the north. The beauty of Samburu County lies primarily in its two picturesque mountains, namely Ololokwe and Koigotor.</string>
    <string name = "eldoret_03">Eldoret is one of the fastest growing towns of Kenya. Nestled south of the Cherangani Hills in the verdant landscape, it is one of African paradises where everything you see has the touch of natural beauty still unadulterated by the intruding modernity. Being the bureaucratic center of Uasin Gishu District of the Rift Valley Province, makes it an even more preferable place as you can find modern amenities, lodgings and more to ensure that your stay is more worthwhile. </string>
    <string name = "kakamega_04">Kakamega is a town that is located in the western Kenya. It lies about 30 km north of the Equator. The town is densely population and is the headquarters of the Kakamega County. Located 50 km north of Kisumu that is the third largest city of Kenya as well as a port city lying on the Lake Victoria, the average elevation of Kakamega is 1,535 metres.</string>
    <string name = "nakuru_05">One important thing that you need to know about Nakuru is that it lies in vicinity to the most prominent destinations of the world including Kenya’s capital Nairobi and Masai Mara. In addition to this, the attractive district is also home to the Menangai Crater which is the second largest volcanic crater of the world.</string>
    <string name = "meru_06">Meru is a city in the Meru County of Kenya. It is situated in the Eastern Highlands of Kenya and serves as the headquarters of Meru County. Located at an elevation, Meru is a thriving urban centre that is also home to several rivers, mountains and other natural elements. The beauty of Meru is highlighted with thirteen rivers and many mountain-fed streams spread all over the terrain.</string>
    <string name = "narok_07">Traversing three hours west of Nairobi, this crumbling provincial town which is also the capital of the Mara region. It is the final proper centre prior to the vast grasslands of the Masai Mara. It is a surprising and friendly hassle free place that offers few travellers with a reason to stop and unwind. A lot of people roll on in, browse the curio shops when the driver refuels before you begin rolling on out again.</string>
    <string name = "mombasa_08">Mombasa is situated in south-east Kenya along the Indian Ocean. It is a beautiful coastal city that is known as the blue and white city. It is also the oldest city in the country, with a rich and vibrant cultural history. The enthralling city of Mombasa is known for its exceptional natural beauty. This city is famous for its pristine beaches, turquoise blue sea, coral reefs and thick vegetation of lush green palms. </string>
    <string name = "kitale_09">Kitale is a beautiful agricultural town that is located in the Western Kenya. It lies some 380 kilometres from Nairobi which is the capital of Kenya. The town lies between Mount Elgon and Cherengani Hills. The significant cash crops which are grown in Kitale include seed maize, sunflower, Pyrethrum, tea, seed beans and coffee. </string>
    <string name = "thika_10">Thika is indeed one of the most discernible names to have emerged from the colonial Kenya all accredited to the articulate memoir which is Elspeth Huxley’s, ‘The Flame Trees of Thika.’ These days, in the growing modern city, you’ll actually be hard pressed to locate a tree let alone a flame tree. However, you still have an opportunity to indulge in the tiny nostalgia before you finally get back on the highway and continue further on the way.</string>
    <string name = "kisumu_11">Kisumu is nestled on the sloping shore Winam Gulf of the Lake Victoria. It may be the third largest town of Kenya but its relaxed atmosphere is way different from that of Mombasa and Nairobi. play an active role in boosting the economy of Kisumu by making a visit to the town.</string>
    <string name = "giraffe_manor_12">Giraffe Manor happens to be an offbeat and exclusive boutique hotel in Nairobi which is owned and operated by The Safari Collection. It is referred to as one of the most sought after properties in the whole world. Spread over an area of about 12 acres of private land in the midst of 140 acres of indigenous forest, this is an icon in itself. The heritage manor house had an extraordinary appeal that dates back to almost 1930s when visitors and wildlife enthusiasts came to Eastern Africa to indulge in wildlife safaris.</string>
    <string name = "amboseli_national_park_13">Located in the southern part of Kenya, the Amboseli National Park is one of the most exciting places to visit in Kenya in December with your loved ones. This park is famous for the majestic beauty of Mount Kilimanjaro that you can see on the horizon and large herds of grazing wild elephants. This National Park comprises five main divisions of wildlife habitats namely the open plains, rocky thorn bush country, acacia woodland, marshlands and swamps.</string>
    <string name = "mt_kenya_14">Spread over a vast area of 715 square km, Mount Kenya National Park was established in 1949, to protect Mount Kenya and its surrounding biodiversity. This National Park protects the wildlife of the area and acts as a catchment of Kenya’s water supply, and it is one of the best places to visit in Kenya. Apart from tourists, this park also attracts climbers, hikers and adventure lovers all year round.</string>
    <string name = "lake_victoria_15">Lake Victoria is also known as Victoria Nyanza and is the largest lake in Africa making it one of the best places to visit in Kenya. It was named Lake Victoria, by British explorer John Hanning Speke. The vast lake is spread over an area of 69,484 square km and preserves more than 200 species of fishes. Amongst them, the ‘Tilapia’ is the most abundant variety and can be seen swimming on the surface of the lake.</string>
    <string name = "lake_naivasha_16">Lake Naivasha is a freshwater lake in Kenya and a part of the Great Rift Valley. The name ‘Naivasha’ is derived from the native Maasai language ‘Nai’posha’ means ‘rough water’. Due to sudden storms, the water turns very rough in this lake, which is the phenomenon from which the lake gets its name. This lake is one of the most popular places to visit in Kenya due to its natural beauty. </string>
    <string name = "samburu_national_reserve_17">The Samburu National Reserve was established in 1985. It is a game reserve situated on the banks of River Ewaso Ng’iro in Kenya. Spread over a sprawling area of 165 square km it is one of the best places to visit in Kenya due to the ecological wealth that it possesses. This reserve is home to almost 900 wild elephants, leopards, lions and cheetahs. You can also spot the famous Kamunyak Lion when you are taking a magical safari through this park. </string>
    <string name = "diani_beach_18">Diani Beach is amongst the most scenic places to visit in Kenya, where you can relax and unwind and take in the serenity of nature. Surrounded by the vast Indian Ocean, this mesmerising beach is famous for its soft white sand, the pleasant ocean waves and a thick outgrowth of swaying palm trees. The beach is lined with restaurants and snack stations serving authentic local delicacies, shopping centres and supermarkets.</string>
    <string name = "manda_bay_19">Manda Bay is an enchanting boutique-lodge situated at the northern part of Manda Island in the Limu archipelago along the Kenyan coastline. This privately owned lodge is the perfect escape, where you can unwind and relax amidst the pristine beauty of Kenya.</string>
    <string name = "_great_rift_valley_20">The Great Rift valley is one of the best places to visit in Kenya, which consists of an enormous valley and is a series of geographical trenches stretching over a distance of 7000 km from Bekaa Valley in Lebanon to Mozambique in South Africa. A vast stretch of this valley runs through Kenya, dividing the country into two parts. It is a place of incredible natural beauty where you can see infinite stretches of valleys, mountains and rivers that have existed for millions of years. </string>
    <string name = "uhuru_gardens_21">The word ‘Uhuru’ means ‘freedom’ in Swahili. The Uhuru Gardens is a memorial park in Nairobi, which symbolises the celebration of independence from British rule in 1963. This park also celebrates the inauguration of Jomo Kenyatta – the first president of Kenya. The park consists of a statue of a soldier holding up the Kenyan flag. The fountain in the park symbolises ‘Twenty-Five years of Uhuru- peace, love and unity monument.’ </string>
    <string name = "lamu_island_22">Founded in the 12th century, the picturesque island of Lamu is one of the oldest and most authentic surviving centres that uphold the Swahili tradition in all of East Africa. It is also a very popular tourist town, where you can stay in some of the best hotels and resorts, explore hidden beaches and a thriving local culture. People of many ethnicities and speaking many languages have made their homes on this island, which makes it a unique and colourful urban centre.</string>
    <string name = "wasini_island_23">If you are looking for offbeat places to visit in Kenya, then you can check out the quaint island of Wasini, which was originally inhabited by Chinese people. Even today, the island doesn’t have proper roads or means of transportation. Cargo and goods are transported by foot or by boats. The roads are made of coral or sand. However, the natural beauty of the island makes it popular amongst tourists. The island has some of the best beaches and the waters around the island are home to whales, dolphins and colourful tropical fish. </string>
    <string name = "mount_longonot_24">This volcano is one of the best places to visit in Kenya in December due to the natural beauty and the colourful history that this place is known for. Even though it is still known as a local volcano, the last time it erupted was in the 1860s. This is the perfect destination for trekkers and adventure lovers since there are several hiking and trekking trails to explore. The name of the mountain is derived from the steep ridges and difficult terrain that makes this mountain distinctive.</string>
    <string name = "hells_gate_25">Hell’s Gate National Park is situated in the southern part of Lake Naivasha and to the north-west of Nairobi. It was established in 1984. The park is spread over an area of 68.25 square km. The park is home to a wide variety of wild animals like lions, cheetahs, leopards along with the rare lammergeier vultures, Hyraxes, eland, African buffalos, zebras, hartebeest, Thomson’s gazelle, baboons and Hyenas. </string>
    <string name = "tsavo_national_park_26">Tsavo National Park is one of the oldest and largest parks in Kenya, covering an area of 13,747 square km. This park was established in 1948. A large part of this park is covered by semi-arid grassland and savannah. It is home to a vast number of magnificent animals and birds. It preserves the famous “Big Five” comprising the endangered Black Rhino, lions, elephants, leopards and the cape buffalos. A mind-boggling variety of birds such as the crowned cranes, lovebirds, black kites and sacred ibis are found in abundance.</string>
    <string name = "lake_nakuru_27">Lake Nakuru is a beautiful lake of Kenya that is largely known for its humongous variety of pink flamingos. A large number of birds’ throng on the lake every day. Lake Nakuru is one of the Rift Valley soda lakes which comprises of almost one third of the Lake Nakuru National Park area.</string>
    <string name = "fourteen_falls_28">Fourteen Falls is a spectacular waterfall in proximity to the Thika town. It offers a complete 27 meter deep scenery. There is so much to see and do at the Fourteen Falls. Some of the most prominent activities of the region include plant identification, photography, boating, bird watching, fishing, among the others. The falls get its name from the 14 different waterfalls that can be found on the broad section of the popular Athi River.</string>
    <string name = "shaba_national_reserve_29">Shaba National Reserves is known for its rich wildlife and unique variety of birds making this national reserve so popular worldwide. Tourists coming here can spot some rare species of animals, including Reticulated giraffes, Grevy\'s zebra, Beisa oryx, the Somali ostrich, and the Gerenuk. Apart from these species that are exclusive to this region, you can also spot a few common wildlife creatures, including Elephant, black rhino, lion, leopard, cheetah, buffalo and hyena.</string>
    <string name = "buffalo_springs_national_reserve_30">If you\'re a wildlife buff then a wildlife tour to Buffalo Springs National Reserve, in Isiolo County of Kenya, should be on top of your travelling list. The Buffalo Springs National Reserve is the hidden wildlife gem of the country. This place is known for unique and exotic flora and fauna like lava terraces, rolling grasslands, doum palms, forests, scrub brush, Ewaso Nyiro River, and of course the buffalo springs, the main center of attraction here. </string>
    <string name = "ol_pejeta_conservancy_31">Nestled in the foothills of the majestic Mount Kenya and spread across a vast area of whopping 36,400 hectares, the Ol Pejeta Conservancy is famed for housing the last two northern white rhinoceros in the world. This protected area is also known to be one of East Africa’s largest black rhino sanctuaries.</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about the day.</string>
</resources>